Guide to the ACT UP New York records, 1969, 1982-1997 [bulk 1987-1995]
The New York Public Library. Manuscripts and Archives Division.
- Series IV. Actions, demonstrations, and zaps, 1987-1995, n.d.; 556059; 7 boxes
  - 1990, 556096
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS) action, New York, 556108
      - 1990 Jun 19, 556109 (Reel 11, Box 16, Folder 6)
      - 1990 Jun 19, 556110 (Reel 12, Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Puerto Rico action, San Juan, Puerto Rico, 556111
      - 1990 Aug, 556112 (Reel 11, Box 16, Folder 7)
      - 1990 Aug, 556113 (Reel 12, Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Centers for Disease Control (CDC) action, Atlanta, Georgia, 1990 Dec 3; 556114 (Reel 12, Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Stop the Church II and other related actions, 1989 Dec-1990 Jan, 1990 Aug-1991 Jan, n.d; 556115; Contains documents concerning pretrial demonstrations and other related actions. (Reel 13, Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Miller/Phillip Morris boycott, 1990; 556116 (Reel 11, Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Demonstrations, Albany, New York, 1990; 556117 (Reel 11, Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Demonstrations, Atlanta, Georgia, 1990; 556118 (Reel 12, Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Demonstrations: Needle exchange, 1990; 556119 (Reel 11, Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Demonstrations: Miscellaneous, 1990; 556120 (Reel 12, Box 17, Folder 1-2)
  - 1991, 556121
    - Day of Desperation, New York, 1991 Jan 23; 556122 (Reel 12, Box 17, Folder 3-4)
    - Fourth anniversary action, Wall Street, New York, 1991 Apr 2; 556123 (Reel 12, Box 17, Folder 5-6)
    - National health action, Washington, [DC], 1991 May 13; 556124 (Reel 12, Box 17, Folder 7)
    - United Nations, 1991 Jun 19; 556125 (Reel 12, Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Slay the AMA," [American Medical Association] Chicago, Illinois, 1991 Jun 25; 556126 (Reel 12, Box 17, Folder 9)
    - INS action, 1991 Jun 26; 556127 (Reel 12, Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Department of Correctional Services (DOCS), New York, 1991 Jul 9; 556128 (Reel 12, Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Target Bush: 30 Days of Action, Kennebunkport, Maine to the White House, 556129; See Series XV. Addenda for additional materials.
      - 1991 Sep 1, 556130 (Reel 13, Box 18, Folder 3)
      - 1991 Sep 1-30, 556131 (Reel 13, Box 17, Folder 12-13)
      - 1991 Sep 30, 556132 (Reel 13, Box 18, Folder 4)
      - 1991 Sep-Oct, 556133 (Reel 13, Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Blue Cross, 1991 Sep 6; 556134 (Reel 13, Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Mandatory healthcare workers, New York, 1991 Sep 11; 556135; Also known as the "Doctors in Chains" action. (Reel 13, Box 18, Folder 1)
    - AIDS Treatment Activists Conference 2 (ATAC 2), 1991 Sep 27-29; 556136 (Reel 13, Box 18, Folder 2)
    - National healthcare, Washington, [DC], 1991 Oct 1; 556137 (Reel 13, Box 18, Folder 5)
    - White House working group, 1991 Nov; 556138 (Reel 13, Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Demonstrations: Miscellaneous, 1991; 556139 (Reel 13, Box 18, Folder 7)
  - 1992, 556140
    - New Hampshire, 1992 Jan 10; 556141 (Reel 13, Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Ashes, [Washington,] DC, 1992 Oct; 556142 (Reel 13, Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Quayle dinner, 1992 Oct; 556143 (Reel 13, Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Republican convention (proposed), 1992 Aug; 556144 (Reel 13, Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Little Rock action, [Little Rock, Arkansas], 1992 Nov 3; 556145 (Reel 13, Box 18, Folder 15)
    - United Nations, 1992 Dec 1; 556146 (Reel 13, Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Activism, 1992; 556147 (Reel 14, Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Presidential election demonstrations, 1992; 556148 (Reel 13, Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Stop the Church, 1992; 556149 (Reel 13, Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Demonstrations: Miscellaneous, 1992; 556150 (Reel 14, Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Demonstrations: TB, 1992 Feb, n.d; 556151 (Reel 14, Box 19, Folder 2)
  - 1994, 556152
    - City hall action, New York, 1994 Jan 3; 556153 (Reel 14, Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Target Rudy [Giuliani] action, New York, 1994 Mar 22; 556154 (Reel 14, Box 19, Folder 6)
  - 1995, 556155
    - Newt [Gingrich] at the Hilton, New York, 1995 Apr 24; 556156 (Reel 14, Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Twenty-fifth action, New York, 1995 Apr 25; 556157 (Reel 14, Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Gay pride actions, New York, 1988 Aug, 1989 May-Jun, 1993 Jun, 1994 Jun, n.d; 556158 (Reel 14, Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Zap/action teach-in outline, n.d.; 556159 (Reel 14, Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous actions, n.d.; 556160 (Reel 14, Box 19, Folder 11)
- Series V. Financial records, 1989-1994 [?], n.d; 556161; 5 boxes
  Series V. Financial records is arranged alphabetically; it consists of assorted financial records including bills, receipts, invoices, cancelled checks, and auction records. There are also some records for the Auction for ACT UP held on December 3, 1989 in New York City, co-chaired by David Hockney and Annie Leibovitz. See Series XV. Addenda for additional financial records.
  - Auction, 556162
    - Auction for Action, circa 1989 Dec; 556163; Folders 7-13, containing unpaid lots and silent auction bids, were not microfilmed.; Catalog, unpaid lots, silent auction bids, forms, and envelopes (Reel 17, Box 23, Folder 6-14)
    - Incoming auction checks, 1989, n.d.; 556164; Not microfilmed (Box 23, Folder 1-5)
  - Incoming checks, 1991; 556165; Not microfilmed (Box 24, Folder 2-3)
  - Fact/contribution sheets, n.d.; 556166 (Reel 17, Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Fashion for Action receipts, 1991; 556167 (Reel 17, Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Merchandise order forms, 556168 (Reel 17, Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Paid bills and receipts, 556169
    - Bills, 1992-1993; 556170 (Reel 16, Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Paid bills, 1990; 556171 (Reel 15, Box 20, Folder 1-15)
    - Paid bills and receipts, 1991; 556172 (Reel 16, Box 21, Folder 2-11)
    - Receipts: People of Color conference, 1991; 556173 (Reel 16, Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Office accounts, 556174
    - MTS [Multitasking Systems] photocopying, 1994 [?] Mar; 556175 (Reel 16, Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Offset Printing invoice, n.d.; 556176 (Reel 16, Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Pitney Bowes, n.d.; 556177 (Reel 16, Box 22, Folder 15-16)
    - Postage, 556178
      - By phone, n.d.; 556179 (Reel 16, Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Meter settings, n.d.; 556180 (Reel 16, Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Staples account, receipts, and invoices, 556181 (Reel 16, Box 22, Folder 1-5)
  - Office equipment, 556182
    - Mobius computer owner's manual, n.d.; 556183 (Reel 16, Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Printer, n.d.; 556184 (Reel 16, Box 22, Folder 14)
    - New printer, n.d.; 556185 (Reel 16, Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Tell it to ACT UP, 1992; 556186; Tell it to ACT UP is an internal newsletter. These issues deal with financial matters. Other issues are located in Series X. Publications and near-print materials, X.D. Newsletters and serials, under the ACT UP grouping. (Reel 16, Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Workspace lease, n.d.; 556187 (Reel 17, Box 24, Folder 6)
- Series VI. Chapters, 1986-1993, n.d.; 556188; 4 boxes
  Series VI. Chapters is arranged in two subseries: VI.A. United States, 1986-1993, n.d., and VI.B. International, n.d. It should be noted that although ACT UP New York was the founding chapter, it did not act as the organization's national headquarters; each chapter was autonomous. Materials in this series provide evidence of ACT UP's activities outside of New York. The bulk of the series focuses on chapters established in the United States. Of these, the Los Angeles chapter was the largest and most well documented. There is some information on how chapters adapted in locales more conservative than New York City. Outside of the continental United States, a chapter was established in Puerto Rico. International chapters documented here include Amsterdam, Barcelona, Berlin, Brussels, Cape Town, Europe, Köln, London, Melbourne, Milano, Montréal, Moscow, Paris, Sydney, and Vancouver.
  - VI.A. United States, 1986-1993, n.d.; 556189; 3 boxes and 15 folders
    Subseries VI.A. United States is arranged alphabetically by state, followed by the commonwealth of Puerto Rico.
    - Pheonix, Arizona, n.d.; 556190 (Reel 18, Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Arkansas, 556191
      - n.d, 556192 (Reel 18, Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Little Rock, n.d.; 556193 (Reel 18, Box 25, Folder 3)
    - California, 556194
      - Central Valley, n.d.; 556195 (Reel 18, Box 25, Folder 4)
      - East Bay, n.d.; 556196 (Reel 18, Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Long Beach, n.d.; 556197 (Reel 19, Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Los Angeles, 556198
        - n.d, 556199 (Reel 19, Box 26, Folder 8-9)
        - 1990, 556200 (Reel 18, Box 26, Folder 1-3)
        - 1991-1993, 556201 (Reel 19, Box 26, Folder 4-6)
        - Minutes, 1990 May-1992; 556202 (Reel 18, Box 25, Folder 6-15)
        - Position paper: AIDS policy, 1990; 556203 (Reel 19, Box 26, Folder 7)
        - Tiara, n.d.; 556204; Newsletter (Reel 19, Box 26, Folder 10)
        - Treatment and Data committee report, 1991; 556205 (Reel 18, Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Orange County, n.d.; 556206 (Reel 19, Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Redwood region, n.d.; 556207 (Reel 19, Box 26, Folder 13)
      - San Francisco, 556208
        - n.d, 556209 (Reel 19, Box 26, Folder 14)
        - Golden Gate, n.d.; 556210 (Reel 19, Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Colorado, n.d.; 556211 (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 1)
    - New Haven, Connecticut, n.d.; 556212; See Series XV. Addenda for additional materials. (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 2)
    - District of Columbia (DC), n.d.; 556213 (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Florida, 556214
      - Miami, n.d.; 556215 (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Tallahassee, n.d.; 556216 (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Tampa Bay, n.d.; 556217 (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Atlanta, Georgia, n.d.; 556218 (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Idaho, n.d.; 556219 (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Chicago, Illinois, n.d.; 556220 (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Louisiana, 556221
      - Monroe, n.d.; 556222 (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 10)
      - New Orleans, n.d.; 556223 (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Shreveport, n.d.; 556224 (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Maine, 556225
      - n.d, 556226 (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 17)
      - Portland, 556227 (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Baltimore, Maryland, 556228 (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Massachusetts, 556229
      - Boston, n.d.; 556230 (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Provincetown, n.d.; 556231 (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Western, n.d.; 556232 (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Michigan, 556233
      - Ann Arbor, n.d.; 556234 (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 19)
      - Detroit, n.d.; 556235 (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Minnesota, 556236
      - 1986-1989, 556237 (Reel 19, Box 27, Folder 21)
      - 1990-1992, 556238 (Reel 20, Box 27, Folder 22-24)
    - Missouri, 556239
      - Kansas City, n.d.; 556240 (Reel 20, Box 27, Folder 25)
      - St. Louis, n.d.; 556241 (Reel 20, Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Nebraska, n.d.; 556242 (Reel 20, Box 27, Folder 27)
    - New Hampshire, n.d.; 556243 (Reel 20, Box 27, Folder 28)
    - New Jersey, n.d.; 556244 (Reel 20, Box 27, Folder 29-31)
    - New York, 556245
      - Youth chapter, Albany, n.d.; 556246 (Reel 20, Box 27, Folder 32)
      - Ithaca, n.d.; 556247 (Reel 20, Box 27, Folder 34)
      - Long Island, 556248 (Reel 20, Box 27, Folder 35)
      - Western, n.d.; 556249 (Reel 20, Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Ohio, 556250
      - Cincinnati, n.d.; 556251 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Cleveland, 556252 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Columbus, n.d.; 556253 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Oberlin, n.d.; 556254 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, n.d.; 556255 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Portland, Oregon, 556256 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania, 556257
      - Philadelphia, n.d.; 556258 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Pittsburgh, 1990 Nov, 1991 Mar, n.d; 556259 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Rhode Island, 556260 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 9)
    - South Dakota, n.d.; 556261 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Texas, 556262
      - Austin, n.d.; 556263 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Houston, n.d.; 556264 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Seattle, Washington, n.d.; 556265 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Madison/Milwaukee, Wisconsin, n.d.; 556266 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Puerto Rico, n.d.; 556267 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 15)
  - VI.B. International, n.d.; 556268; 15 folders
    - Australia, 556269
      - Melbourne, n.d.; 556270 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 16)
      - Sydney, n.d.; 556271 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Brussels, Belgium, n.d.; 556272 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Canada, 556273
      - Vancouver, British Columbia, n.d.; 556274 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 19)
      - Montréal, Québec, n.d.; 556275 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 20)
    - London, England, 556276 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Europe, n.d.; 556277 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Paris, France, n.d.; 556278; See Series XV. Addenda for additional materials. (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Germany, 556279
      - Berlin, n.d.; 556280 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 22)
      - Köln, n.d.; 556281 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Milano, Italy, n.d.; 556282 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Amsterdam, The Netherlands, 556283 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Barcelona, Spain, n.d.; 556284 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Cape Town, South Africa, n.d.; 556285 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Moscow, Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1990, n.d.; 556286 (Reel 20, Box 28, Folder 29)
- Series VII. Committees, 1985-1995, n.d.; 556287; 45 boxes
  Series VII. Committees is one of the largest series in the collection; it is arranged in three subseries: VII.A. General committees, 1985, 1987-1995, n.d.; VII.B. Insurance and Healthcare Access committee, 1988-1995, n.d.; and VII.C. Treatment and Data committee, 1986-1994, n.d.
  This series contains correspondence, handouts, reports, and related material. The committees provided the framework to collate information and pursue specific concerns. Represented along with the committees are the working groups that were temporary in nature, occasionally evolving into permanent committees. Some committees and working groups are not represented in this series.
  - VII.A. General committees, 1985, 1987-1995, n.d; 556288; 18 boxes
    Subseries VII.A. General committees is arranged alphabetically; it includes correspondence, handbills, journal articles, minutes, press clippings, reports, subject files, and related material.
    The committees represented in this subseries include: AIDS Cure Project, Alternative and Holistic committee, Barbara McClintock Project to Cure AIDS, Coordinating committee, Democratic National Reform, DIVA TV (Damned Interfering Video Activists TV), Foreign National caucus, Gay Games Boycott working group, Immigration working group, Media committee, People of Color working group, and TB working group.
    The Coordinating committee was primarily administrative. It facilitated and handled routine business for which the floor did not have time. The Media committee was responsible for gathering published information about AIDS/HIV-related health, social, and political issues from newspapers, magazines, and scholarly journals. This information, referred to as "back table literature," was collated and made available to ACT UP members. Information found in the Media committee files is supplemented by Series VIII. Subjects and Series X. Published and near-print materials.
    - ACT UP against the New World Order, n.d.; 556289 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 1)
    - ACT UP Americas, n.d.; 556290 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Action committee, n.d.; 556291 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Ad Hoc working group for HR 2872, n.d.; 556292 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Addicts Rights caucus, n.d.; 556293 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 5)
    - AIDS Cure Project working group, n.d.; 556294; Formerly known as the Barbara McClintock Project to Cure AIDS. (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Alternative and Holistic Treatment committee, 556295
      - n.d, 556296 (Reel 24, Box 33, Folder 1-3)
      - n.d, 556297 (Reel 25, Box 33, Folder 4)
      - (General), n.d.; 556298 (Reel 25, Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Alternative therapies for hispanic patients, n.d.; 556299 (Reel 25, Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Background information, 556300
        - American Council on Science and Health, 556301; Affiliate group of the National Council against Health Fraud. (Reel 25, Box 34, Folder 1)
        - The Food and Drug Administration' s attacks on alternative treatments, 556302 (Reel 25, Box 34, Folder 2)
        - Suppression tactics of the AMA [American Medical Association], n.d.; 556303 (Reel 25, Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Bitter melon as HIV therapy, n.d.; 556304 (Reel 25, Box 33, Folder 9)
      - A brief history of alternative systems of medicine and their suppression in the United States, 556305 (Reel 25, Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Broadsides and handouts, 556306 (Reel 25, Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Caesar's wheat grass, n.d.; 556307 (Reel 25, Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Chinese medicine, n.d.; 556308 (Reel 25, Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Health centers, n.d.; 556309 (Reel 25, Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Health Education AIDS Liasion (HEAL), n.d.; 556310 (Reel 25, Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Insurance and AIDS, 556311 (Reel 25, Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Marijuana, n.d.; 556312 (Reel 25, Box 33, Folder 16)
      - National Action for Freedom of AIDS Treatment Choice, n.d.; 556313 (Reel 25, Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Omnibus, 1994 Sep 9; 556314; Letter, abstracts, and articles (Reel 25, Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Publications, 556315
        - Downtown Pulmonary Center, 1990 Jul; 556316; Information regarding PCP diagnosis (Reel 25, Box 33, Folder 12)
        - Journal articles, n.d.; 556317 (Reel 25, Box 34, Folder 6-8)
        - Journal articles, n.d.; 556318 (Reel 26, Box 34, Folder 9-10)
        - National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases, 1990 May; 556319 (Reel 25, Box 33, Folder 18)
        - New York Naturally: A Resource Directory for Natural Living in New York, 1991; 556320; Not microfilmed (Box 33, Folder 19)
        - Periodicals, n.d.; 556321 (Reel 26, Box 34, Folder 12)
        - Press clippings, n.d.; 556322 (Reel 26, Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Sheet, n.d.; 556323 (Reel 25, Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Vaccine therapies for HIV, n.d.; 556324 (Reel 25, Box 33, Folder 20)
      - Whole Foods Project, n.d.; 556325 (Reel 25, Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Apocalypse Now working group, n.d.; 556326 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Centers for Disease Control working group] (CDC), n.d.; 556327; Listed on the folder as the "Center for Discriminary Concepts (CDC)." (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 9)
    - City Actions working group, n.d.; 556328 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 10)
    - City and State Actions committee, 556329 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Congressional Action working group, n.d.; 556330 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Coordinating committee, 556331
      - Minutes, 1987 Sep-1989; 556332 (Reel 26, Box 35, Folder 2-18)
      - Minutes, 1990-1991; 556333 (Reel 26, Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Minutes, 1992-1995; 556334 (Reel 27, Box 36, Folder 2-3)
      - Start up, 1987 Jun; 556335 (Reel 26, Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Democratic National Platform committee, n.d.; 556336 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Disaster Relief Appeal group, n.d.; 556337 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 14)
    - DIVA TV (Damned Interfering Video Activists TV), n.d.; 556338 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Election 1988 subcommittee, circa 1988; 556339 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Financial Status committee, n.d.; 556340 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Foreign Nationals caucus, n.d.; 556341 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Fundraising committee and Treasurer's reports, 556342 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Gay and Lesbian Teach-in committee, 556343 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Gay Games Boycott working group, n.d.; 556344 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Global Action committee, n.d.; 556345 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Haiti working group, 556346
      - Emergency Coalition for Haitian Regugees, n.d.; 556347 (Reel 27, Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Handbills, 556348 (Reel 27, Box 37, Folder 4-8)
      - Insight newsletter, 1992 Fall, 1994 Mar and Summer; 556349 (Reel 27, Box 37, Folder 18)
      - National Network quarterly meeting, 1993 Jan 9; 556350 (Reel 27, Box 37, Folder 19)
      - Postcards and stickers, 556351 (Reel 27, Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Press clippings, n.d.; 556352 (Reel 27, Box 37, Folder 10-17)
      - Solidarity Week organizing packet, 1993 Feb 7-13; 556353 (Reel 27, Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Target letters, n.d.; 556354 (Reel 27, Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous, n.d.; 556355 (Reel 27, Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Housing committee, n.d.; 556356 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Immigration working group, 556357
      - Clean-out sale, n.d.; 556358 (Reel 28, Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Coalition for Immigration and Refugee Rights and Services, 556359 (Reel 28, Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1992-1993; 556360 (Reel 28, Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Lesbian and Gay Rights Immigration and Asylum Rights Task Force, 556361 (Reel 28, Box 38, Folder 7)
      - New York City Immigration Coalition start-up kit, n.d.; 556362 (Reel 28, Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Posters and handbills, 556363 (Reel 28, Box 38, Folder 4-5)
      - Press clippings, n.d.; 556364; Folder 2 was not microfilmed. (Reel 28, Box 39, Folder 1-13)
      - Press packet, n.d.; 556365; Created by the ACT UP New York Immigration working group. (Reel 28, Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Spanish language, 556366
        - Materials, n.d.; 556367 (Reel 28, Box 38, Folder 11)
        - Materials regarding AIDS and HIV, 556368 (Reel 28, Box 38, Folder 10)
        - Pamphlets, n.d.; 556369 (Reel 29, Box 40, Folder 1-2)
        - Serials, n.d.; 556370 (Reel 29, Box 39, Folder 15)
      - World Health Organization, HIV and AIDS, 556371 (Reel 28, Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous, n.d.; 556372 (Reel 28, Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Interagency Task Force subcommittee, n.d.; 556373 (Reel 21, Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Latino/a caucus, 556374
      - General, n.d.; 556375 (Reel 21, Box 30, Folder 1)
      - ACT UP generated information, n.d.; 556376 (Reel 21, Box 30, Folder 2-3)
      - Broadsides, n.d.; 556377 (Reel 21, Box 30, Folder 4-5)
      - Broadsides and handouts, 556378 (Reel 21, Box 30, Folder 6)
      - El lesbianismo como una cuestión política, 1985 Dec, 1987; 556379; This folder also contains an article from the seminar "Una expresión lésbica en el movimiento proletario." (Reel 21, Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Packets, 556380
        - Argentina, n.d.; 556381 (Reel 21, Box 30, Folder 9)
        - Information, n.d.; 556382 (Reel 21, Box 30, Folder 7-8)
        - Press, n.d.; 556383 (Reel 21, Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Pamphlets (Spanish), n.d.; 556384 (Reel 22, Box 30, Folder 16-19)
      - Pan American Health Organization, n.d.; 556385 (Reel 22, Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Press clippings, n.d.; 556386 (Reel 21, Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Sociedad y SIDA, 1991 Jun; 556387 (Reel 22, Box 30, Folder 13)
      - World Health Organization, n.d; 556388 (Reel 22, Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous, n.d.; 556389 (Reel 22, Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Lesbian and Gay Pride committee, 556390 (Reel 22, Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Majority Actions committee, n.d.; 556391; See Series XV. Addenda for additional materials. (Reel 22, Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Media committee, 556392
      - Articles, n.d.; 556393 (Reel 23, Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Contact lists, n.d.; 556394 (Reel 22, Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1987-1990, n.d.; 556395 (Reel 22, Box 31, Folder 3-5)
      - Notes, n.d.; 556396 (Reel 23, Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Packets, n.d.; 556397 (Reel 23, Box 31, Folder 9-10)
      - Press releases and information packets, 556398